深入黑暗
第一季 第四集
救命啊
Help me, please!
放开...
Let go of--
救命  放开我
Help me! Let me go!
大家好  我是杰西卡・豪尔
Hey, everyone, I'm Jesse Hall,
杰西的《新鲜免费》
《新鲜免费》的主编
the editor of Fresh and Free,
我身边是我们的常驻播主丹妮尔・威廉姆斯
we're joined by our regular contributor Danielle Williams.
新年决心
如何好好度过2018年的最后时刻
大家好
Hi, guys.
丹妮尔・威廉姆斯
她是《健康起来  丹妮尔》的主创
The creator of Get Well Danielle
和非常蔬菜汁的老板
and owner of Very Very Vegetable Juices.
丹妮尔明年将有自己的电视节目开播
Danielle is getting her very own TV show next year.
强有力地说明了展现自己能带来什么
Such a powerful example of what manifestation can bring.
#制作
我们很荣幸你能最后一次来作客
We really are honored you're here with us one last time
激励我们迎接新年
to get us inspired for the new year.
2019年新年  #最棒的一年
好了  何必等到1月1日
Okay, why wait till January 1st?
你可以在午夜钟响前
You can start your health kick
就开始健康生活
before the clock hits midnight
喝这种健康鸡尾酒
with these wellness cocktails
用我的非常蔬菜汁调制的节日混合酒
with my Very Very Vegetable holiday blends.
好了  各位
Now, guys,
别忘记发布你的自爱自拍
don't forget to post your self-love selfies
上传你的自爱自拍
让我看到你和姐妹们一起喝我的鸡尾酒
of you and your pals drinking my cocktails
并加上标签#健康起来丹妮尔
and tag them GetWellDanielle
#健康起来丹妮尔
#新鲜免费
让我看到你们美丽的脸庞
so I can see all of your beautiful faces.
#杰西超棒
#非常非常美味
#更好的我
你对2019年的新开始有什么建议吗
Now what is some advice to start fresh in 2019?
节日有时会让我们失控
The holidays make us feel a little out of control.
点击下面链接查看配方
第三杯蛋酒了哦
Hello, third glass of eggnog.
我们可能会觉得我们无法掌控自己的人生
We might be feeling like we aren't in charge of our own lives.
但你可以掌控的
But you are.
我就要提醒你  你可以的
I am here to remind you that you are.
你可以做到任何
And you can do whatever it is
你决心做的事
you set your mind to.
闭上眼睛  跟我重复
Now, close your eyes and repeat after me.
我能掌控自己的命运
I control my own destiny.
我能掌控我把握住什么
I control what I hold onto.
我能掌控我放弃什么
And I control what I let go of.
I control what I let go of.
-...放弃什么  -很好啊
- ...I let go of. - Very good.
明天又是新的一天
Now, tomorrow is a new day.
很快就将是新的一年了
Soon it will be a new year.
当午夜钟声敲响
And when the clock strikes 12,
我希望你成为新的你  最好的你
I want you to become the new you, the best you,
你一直想成为
the you that you have always wanted to be
但不敢成为的你
but have been too afraid to become.
多一秒都不要耽搁了
Don't put it off for a second longer.
好了  你妈很快要回家了
Okay, your mom's gonna be home soon.
该收拾了
It's time to clean up.
她好酷啊
She is so cool.
我简直等不及她的新节目了
I cannot wait for her new show.
真希望我像她那么漂亮那么酷
I wish I was as pretty and cool as her.
-你就很漂亮很酷了  凯拉  -她是我的启迪
- You are, Kara. - She's my inspiration!
等我长大  我要像她一样
When I grow up, I wanna be just like her.
其实  凯拉  你可以别跳沙发吗
Actually, Kara, can you not jump on the couch?
我真的很怕你会伤到自己
I'm really worried you're gonna hurt yourself.
但我爱自己
But I love myself.
我能掌控自己的命运
I am in control of my own destiny.
我是公主
I am the princess.
好  我觉得某人糖吃多了
Okay, I think somebody had too much sugar.
那些饼干里不含糖
Those cookies didn't have sugar,
是含有枫糖浆  是原始饮食
they had maple syrup, they're paleo.
那是丹妮尔的食谱
They were Danielle's recipe.
凯拉  可以帮我收拾吗
Kara, can you help me clean up?
真不敢相信你可以跟《健康起来  丹妮尔》
I cannot believe you're going to spend New Year's Eve
共度新年
with Get Well Danielle.
她是什么样的人
What's she like?
我不知道  我好久没见过她了
I don't know, I haven't seen her for a really long time.
但你们是高中同学
But you guys were friends in high school.
-嗯  -好闺蜜吗
- Yeah. - Best friends?
是啊
Yep.
你当时就知道她会这么出名这么酷吗
Did you know she was gonna be so famous and cool?
不知道
No.
但你们一起出演学校戏剧了
But you did school plays together.
这倒是
That's true.
你演得好吗
Were you good in them?
还好吧
Uh, I mean, yeah,
我本想去做演员的
I thought I was gonna be an actress,
我还赢过奖项
and I won awards and stuff, so,
看来大家觉得我挺不错的
I guess people thought I was pretty good.
你为什么不再演戏了
Why'd you stop acting?
是因为你的疤吗
Is it because of your scar?
不是
No.
我就是决定去做
I just thought that I wanted to do something that would
更能影响这个世界的事
make more of a difference in the world.
那你为什么成了个保姆
Then why are you a babysitter?
大家好  我是丹妮尔・威廉姆斯
Hey guys, I'm Danielle Williams,
非常蔬菜汁创始人
founder of Very Very Vegetables
很快将作为主持人
and soon-to-be host
为您带来《健康起来  丹妮尔》
of Get Well Danielle,
春季播出
coming to you this spring.
务必收看哦
Make sure you tune in.
新年新气象
有人吗
Hello?
照片好性感  你是我的偶像  我想成为你  少来了  太美了
你为什么总这么赞  爱你  妹子  你太美了  爱你
好嫉妒  你最美了  求口红号
我们可以教你
We can coach you.
我有种强烈的感觉  他们都一种
And I got the distinct vibe they were like,
"我们都可以上你"的意思
"We could both fuck you,"
我就想"还是算了吧"
and I was like, "No, please."
天呐  我爱这双靴子
Oh, my God, I love these boots!
我好喜欢
Oh, I love them!
天呐  我什么都看不到
Oh, my God, I can't see a thing.
天呐  基拉  看
Oh, my God, Kaela, look.
克洛  别闹了
Stop, Chloe, will you stop?
我开车呢
I'm driving.
好吧
Okay.
我去  将近五千呢
Holy fuck, they're nearly $5,000.
什么
What?
太疯狂了
What--that's crazy.
我好想要
I want them.
姐们  那是半年房租
Dude, that's like half a year's rent.
谁能买得起啊
What--who can afford that?
丹妮尔
Danielle.
是啊
Yeah, well...
你紧张吗
Are you nervous?
不  我为什么要紧张
No, why would I be?
怎么  你紧张吗
Why? Are you?
有点
A little.
不
No.
开玩笑吧
You're fucking kidding me.
-我去  -又来
- Shit. - Again?
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我刚保养过车的
I just serviced this fucking car.
看我怎么养你的脸吧
I'm about to service your fucking face.
对不起啦  我们走吧
I'm sorry, okay, let's go.
至少给我一把啊
You would at least have one for me?
抱歉  我只有一把伞
I'm sorry, I only have one umbrella!
-天呐  基拉  -谁会准备两把伞啊
- Jesus, Kaela! - Who has two umbrellas?
玛丽・波平斯吗  我不知道
Mary-fucking-Poppins! I don't know!
看  所以我们不会买五千美元的靴子
You see? This is why we don't buy $5,000 boots.
天呐  拿着拿着
Oh, my gosh, here, take these, take these.
天呐
Oh, my fucking God.
外面下得好大
It's fucking pouring out there.
基拉的破车又坏了
Kaela's shitmobile broke down again.
你们怎么不打给我
Oh, you should have called me,
我会去接你们的
I would have come pick you up.
你能不能别侮辱莎狄
Um, can you not insult Sadie?
它可是陪伴我多年了
She's been with me for years.
好吧  随你  至少你还有车
Fine, whatever, at least you have a car.
天呐
Oh, my God.
这里看上去一点没变
Wow, it looks exactly the same here.
我好喜欢
I love it.
天呐  你父母居然要
God, I can't believe your parents
卖掉这里吗
are selling this place.
我们在这里度过了多少开心时光啊
We had so many good times here.
我不知道
I don't know, I just--
我一想到...还觉得心惊
it still freaks me out just thinking about...
好了  我要上谁才能
Anyway, who does a girl have to fuck around here
喝到杯酒啊
to get a drink, hm?
她今天都想要些怪怪的东西
Oh, she has odd wants today.
等等  我们不等丹妮尔了吗
Wait, shouldn't we wait for Danielle?
你真觉得她会来吗
You really think she's gonna come?
她不是说她会来的吗
Well, she said she would, didn't she?
你给她发短信时她怎么说的
What did she say when you texted her?
她说...
She said...
"那就太棒了
"That would be so amazing.
好久没见过你们了
I haven't seen you girls in so long
而且也很想"  用的数字
and would be gr8," With an eight,
"跟房子道个别
"To say goodbye to the house.
把具体安排用电邮发给我
Just LMK the deets via email
并抄送我的助理
and CC my assist
海莉"
Hailey@GetWellDanielle.Com."
她还有助理呢
Ooh, she has an assistant.
好了  我觉得她八成不会来
Anyway, I think she'll probably flake.
我觉得她会来的
I think she'll come.
真美味
Yes, yum-yum-yum-yum-yum.
你拿香槟酒了吗
Do you have the Champagne?
我还想要好多
I want so much more.
天呐  你们看到那张
Oh, my God, did you guys see
她和莱昂纳多的合照了吗
that picture of her and Leo?
-谁  -迪卡普里奥
- Who? - DiCaprio.
莱昂纳多・迪卡普里奥  天呐  基拉
Leonardo DiCaprio, Jesus, Kaela.
抱歉  我肯定是没看到
Oh, sorry, I must have missed it.
抱歉什么
What are you sorry about?
错过了一张
That you missed a picture
丹妮尔和莱昂纳多・迪卡普里奥的合照吗
of Danielle and Leonardo DiCaprio?
-谁在乎啊  -天呐
- Who cares? - Oh, my God,
我好在乎的
I care so deeply.
她现在都能跟莱昂纳多谈笑风生了
She's just like hanging out with Leo now.
这多疯狂啊  多不可思议啊
You guys, it's insane, like, it's amazing.
另外
Mm, also,
你们看到她新节目的宣告了吗
did you see the announcement about her show?
春季播出
It's coming out in the spring.
嗯  等着瞧吧
Yeah, well, we'll see about that.
-气球  -嗯
- Oh, the balloons. - Yes.
不  我都没问你
Oh, no, I didn't even ask you
你的面试怎么样了
how your interview went.
没什么好说的
Oh, um, it-there's nothing much to tell.
-就是谈完了  -天呐
- It happened. - Oh, my God,
你要回学校了
you're going back to school.
或许吧  最终吧
Maybe, eventually, you know?
我很想完成学业
I'd love to finish my degree,
或许再回研究生院什么的
maybe go back to grad school or something.
那很好
That's great.
嗯  但这个是为了伊甸园酒吧的女招待工作
Yeah, but this was for a hostess job at Eden's Pub.
嗯
Yeah.
我那天好像看到了招工启事
I saw the help wanted sign there the other day.
我没想到你会想去那里工作
I just didn't think you'd want to work there.
我不想
I don't,
但我需要钱来偿还我的学生贷款
but I need to pay my student loans
我毕竟还去了两年
for the two years of college I did go to
然后精神崩溃
before I had a nervous breakdown
辍学了
and dropped out.
不是精神崩溃
It wasn't a nervous breakdown.
就是的
No, it was.
你们觉得丹妮尔一年能
You guys, how much money do you think
挣多少钱
Danielle makes in a year?
如果再算进她能获得的那些免费的东西
I mean, like, if you factor in all the free stuff she gets.
我读到她光是被动收入
I read somewhere she makes like $200,000
就有二十万
in passive income alone,
光是广告什么的
like just from ads and stuff.
肯定可多了
It's gotta be that much.
她家简直...
Her house is fucking--
就是我的梦想之家
it's literally my dream home.
简直像她钻进我脑子里
It's like she went into my brain
把我的梦想之家拿了出来
and plucked out my dream home
拿给了一个建筑师看
and showed it to an architect.
简直疯了
It's insane.
天呐  她肯定一年
God, she's gotta be making
能挣一百万了吧
like a million a year, right?
我真的不知道  克洛
I really don't know, Chlo.
真希望我有钱
I wish I had money.
有名
I was famous.
或者两者都有
Or both.
该死  她来了
Shit, she came.
-准备好了吗  -丹妮尔  你来了
- You ready? - Danielle, you made it!
-不会更好了  -我们都不确定你会来
- As I'll ever be. - ...we weren't sure I was gonna come.
等等  请进
Wait, come on in!
天呐  克洛
Oh, my God, Chlo!
你看上去好棒
You look amazing.
才不啦
Oh, no.
我觉得...算了
I feel like a...whatever.
-哪里  -好了  你看上去也好棒
- Oh, please! - Anyway, so do you, of course.
少来了
Stop.
各位  真抱歉我迟到了
You guys, I am so sorry I'm late,
好无礼
it is so rude.
莱克斯
Lex,
我好感激你今晚请了我来
I am so grateful you invited me tonight.
我本来特别怕被
I was really dreading whatever, like,
拉去洛杉矶的一个讨厌派对
awful party I was gonna be dragged to in LA,
结果...
and...
这样好多了
This is--this is so much better.
是啊  我们怎么可能
Yeah, well, we couldn't imagine
不带上你一起在这个房子里度过最后一个新年
spending the last New Year's in the house without you.
谢谢
Aw, thank you.
天呐
Oh, my God.
你们装饰得太棒了
You guys, this looks amazing.
气球好可爱
These balloons are so cute.
不是吧
Oh, come on,
我太喜欢这种数字气球了
I am obsessed with these number balloons.
是吧
Right?
基拉买的
Kaela bought them.
没什么的
Yeah, it was-- it's nothing,
就一元店淘的
they're like from the 99 cent store.
当然了
Of course.
你的品位一直最好了  基拉
You always have the best taste, Kaela.
记得我妈以前还问我
Do you remember my mom used to ask
我怎么不能穿得像你那么酷
why I didn't dress more funky like you?
是啊  她那么说挺怪的
Yeah, that was weird of her.
-是吧  -是啊
- Right? - Yeah.
我带了礼物来
Oh, I brought presents.
什么
What?
这都是有机
Okay, these are all organic,
植物制品
all vegan.
无动物产品
Cruelty free.
如果你在乎的话
If you give a shit.
-我们在乎的  -全天然
- We do. - All natural.
艾斯特和塔米  好高档
Esther and Tammy, that's so fancy.
给我的好闺蜜什么都不嫌贵
Well, nothing is too good for my girls.
-谢谢  -我觉得这颜色会特别火
- Thank you. - I think that color will go perfect.
这会特别轰动的
This is making a big splash.
还没发布呢  但会...
Not out yet, but like bright--
是一抹亮色
brightens-- brightens everything up.
好啊  谢谢
Cool, thanks.
嗯
Yeah.
不客气
Of course.
天呐  各位
Oh, my God, you guys,
我可以记录下一切吗
can I document this?
你们在意吗
Do you care?
没问题
Sure, yeah.
天呐  我包里都放了什么啊
Jesus, what do I have in here?
简直像辆小丑车
It's like a freaking clown car.
我要往外掏
I'm just gonna be pulling out
兔子和鸭子了
like rabbits and ducks.
好了  大家凑过来
Okay, everybody scrunch in.
莱克斯  来
Lex, come on.
我在中间
I'll be in the middle.
凑过来
Gather 'round.
好了
All right.
挤过来
Scrunch in.
准备好了吗
Ready?
该死  我眨眼了
Oh, shoot, I'm blinking.
再来一张吧
One more, okay?
好
Okay.
大家说"茄子"
Everybody say "Cheese."
健康起来  丹妮尔
Get Well Danielle.
Get Well Danielle!
我就是想说
Well, I'm just saying that I just feel like
有女人参与的事
just because a woman is involved in something
未必就女权了
doesn't make it inherently feminist,
我觉得我们需要注意这个
and I think that's something we have to watch out for,
你得警醒
like you've gotta be aware
钱和社会机器
that money and this whole machine
会让一切变质
co-opts everything, right?
-好吧  -你们每次希望我闭嘴
- Okay. - You guys always just say okay
都会说"好吧"
when you want me to shut up.
不  我赞同你  基拉
No, I'm with you, Kaela.
我太醉了  不能聊这个
I'm too drunk for this conversation.
基拉
Oh, Kaela,
可以别放多脂奶油吗
do you mind leaving out the heavy cream?
我DF
I'm DF.
什么
DF?
不吃乳制品
Dairy-free.
等等  你有意不吃乳制品吗
Wait, you're dairy-free by choice?
是啊  这对你没什么好处的
Yeah, it's really bad for you.
我才不管呢
I do not care.
我是永远不可能放弃奶酪的
There's no way I could give up cheese.
相信我  我知道
Ugh, trust me, I know,
我好想念奶酪的
I miss cheese so freaking much.
你不吃乳制品多久了
So like how long have you been DF?
四年了吧
Like four years now?
我的一个粉丝发私信说
Yeah, one of my subscribers sent me a message
她脑袋上长了很痛的疖子
saying she had these like terrible painful boils on her head.
疖子
Boils?
是啊  她试了各种药
Yeah, and she tried all of these different medicines
-都不好使  -恶心死了
- and nothing worked. - Oh, that's so gross.
可吓人了
It was really fucked up.
她求着我帮忙
And she was like begging me for help.
但她知道你不是医生吧
But she knew you weren't a doctor though, right?
那无所谓的
Yeah, it didn't matter.
她找过医生了
She had tried doctors
但什么都不好使
and nothing was working.
我就研究了一下
So I did some research
发现乳制品能引起发炎
and found that dairy can cause inflammation issues.
我还读到了其他
And then I started reading about all this other, like,
乳制品对身体的可怕影响  我就想
horrible stuff dairy does to your body and was like,
"我真不该吃乳制品的"
"Whoa, I should not be eating dairy."
听上去你真的产生了积极影响
Wow, it sounds like you're really making a difference.
是啊  这很有满足感
Yeah, I mean, it's totally rewarding,
但是
but, um...
也很辛苦的
it's also a lot of hard work
压力很大
and a ton of pressure.
有时候我会希望
You know, sometimes I just wish
我还跟你们在这里
I was back here with you guys,
像以前那样傻乐呵
just goofing off like we used to.
相信我  你不想的
Believe me, you don't.
相信我  我想的
Believe me, I do.
月亮总是别人家的圆嘛
Well, I think the grass is always greener, you know?
是啊  你说得对
No, you're right, you're right.
我该对我所拥有的感到感激
I should be grateful for what I have.
我是对我所拥有的感到感激
I mean, I am grateful for what I have,
但是
it's just, you know,
有时候你很容易适应了新的平衡
it's sometimes so easy to get accustomed to a new equilibrium
而忘记了自己多么幸运
and forget how lucky you are.
人性吧
Human nature, I guess.
该死
Ah, fuck.
该死  你没事吧
Shit, are you okay?
该死
Ah, fuck.
来
Here.
我没事的
Hey, I'll be fine, I just...
真没事吗
Are you sure?
阿莱克西斯  你真会做饭
Alexis, you are such a good cook.
这些看上去好棒
This all looks so amazing.
嗯  谢谢  莱克斯
Yeah, thank you, Lex.
好香啊
Smells incredible.
谢谢
Thank you.
美味
Yummy.
等等  我们开始前
Wait, um, before we start,
你们能迁就我一下吗
would you guys humor me with something?
当然
Yeah, sure.
我知道这挺俗的
Okay, I know this is a little corny,
但毕竟我们要跨年了
but it is the end of the year, after all,
我觉得如果我们能围坐在桌边
and I think it would be really productive
夸夸自己这一年来
if we just like went around the table
最骄傲的成就
and celebrated ourselves
会很有好处
by acknowledging our proudest accomplishments of the year.
是啊  挺傻的
I know, it's silly,
就是提醒一下自己  我们有怎样的能力嘛
it's just, you know, to remind ourselves of what we're capable of.
好啊  挺好的
Yeah, sure, that's nice.
-好吗  -好
- Yeah? - Okay.
-你先来吧  -我先来
- You go first. - I'll go first.
我志愿  我先来
I volunteered, so I'll go first.
你请
All you.
好吧
Okay, um,
我想我今年最骄傲的成就
I guess my proudest accomplishment this year
就是我接纳了一个情况特别艰难的孩子
would be that I had a really challenging kid come in,
她耳聋  还自闭
um, she was deaf and autistic,
她有...
and, you know, she has like--
很多感官问题
she had a lot of sensory issues.
然后...
And, um,
我不想说得太多愁善感
I don't want to get too mumbo-jumbo-y,
但真的
but it was just-- it was really--
感觉很棒
it's really cool to just--
看到一个人在这么短的时间
to watch a person develop so much
成长这么多
over such a short period of time.
所以
So...
基拉  真是太棒了
Kaela, that is incredible.
你绝对完爆我们所有人
You definitely put the rest of us to shame.
-不  -是的
- No. - Oh yeah.
你真是位出色的女人
You are a fucking amazing woman.
好吧  谢谢
Okay, well, thank you,
我觉得不是  但随便吧
I don't think so, but, you know, whatever.
-换别人换别人  -我觉得你就是
- Someone else, someone else. - Well, I think you are.
克洛
Chlo?
-随你怎么想吧  -好吧
- Whatever you want. - All right, well, okay,
尽管我妈生病了
even though my mom's sick
我没有工作
and I don't have a job
我还破产了
and I'm broke
而且我网上约会了两百次
and I've been on over 200 internet dates
但还是单身
and I still don't have a boyfriend,
我今天没有自杀
I didn't fucking kill myself this year,
敬这个  对吧
so cheers to that, huh?
我开玩笑呢
I'm kidding.
老天  丹妮尔  这是个玩笑
Oh, my God, Danielle, I'm joking.
好吧  放开所有玩笑
Okay, well, all jokes aside, um...
你看起来很受伤  克洛
it seems like you're actually really hurting, Chlo,
我想让你知道
and I want you to know
如果你需要我  我就在这
that I'm here for you if you ever need me.
谢谢
Thank you.
-我爱你  -我爱你
- I love you. - I love you.
莱克斯
Lex?
好吧  克洛和基拉知道
Um, well, as Chloe and Kaela know,
今年其实
this year was actually
对我来说很艰难
especially challenging for me.
天哪
Fuck.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你想跟大家分享一下吗
Is it--is it something you want to share or...?
就是有很多后悔的事
Just a lot of, you know, um... regrets?
感觉我没有活出最好的自己
Feeling like I didn't live my best life.
浪费了很多时间
I wasted a lot of time.
我不知道  只是
I don't know, I--I just had
我有很多愿望和梦想和幻想
all these um, hopes and dreams and visions,
但我只是
but I just, um...
嗯
Yeah, so,
其实没完成什么事情
I didn't actually accomplish a lot this year.
其实好多年都这样了
Actually, for a lot of years.
我觉得自己在过去停滞不前
I feel like I've kind of been bogged down by the past.
紧紧抓着那些
Holding onto things that really I--
我本该放手的东西
I should have let go of.
所以
So...
总之
Anyway, um,
我知道今年快要结束了
I know it's almost the end of the year,
但我真的觉得我最大的成就
but I really feel like my biggest accomplishments
还没有到来
have yet to come.
莱克斯
Wow, Lex.
我喜欢这态度
I loved that.
没错  总归还是时间
Yes, there is always more time,
干杯
so cheers.
Cheers.
敬我们自己
Cheers to us!
等等  你那时在哪
Ha, wait, where were you?
我在看《等待古夫曼》
I was watching Waiting for Guffman.
什么
What?
对啊  我都不知道发生了什么
Yeah, I had no idea that was going on.
你有没有  他射在裤子了
Did you--he jizzed in his pants?
是啊  太疯狂了
Yeah, dude, it was crazy.
他就  他要来亲我
He like--he went in to kiss me
他喊了一声
and then he was like ugh,
然后往后退
and he backed up.
我就问他  "发生什么了"
And I was like, "What's happening?"
然后他不想让我靠近他的裤裆
And like he just didn't want me anywhere near his crotch.
然后我意识到他射在裤子里了
And then I realized it was because he had jizzed in his pants.
我真不敢相信你从没告诉过我
I can't believe you never told me that.
你们知道吗
Did you guys know that?
知道
Yeah.
青春期的男孩真变态
Teenage boys are so weird.
真恶心
So gross.
莱克斯  你还记得
Lex, do you remember the night
你和诺亚・斯皮瓦克亲热的那晚
that you were making out with Noah Spivak
我从地板上爬过去
and I like crawled across the floor
把灯的开关拔了吗
and unplugged the light?
当然记得
Yes, I do.
等等  那是不是他说"小穴"的那晚
Wait, was the same night he said "VJ"?
-是的  -我的天
- Yes. - Oh, my God,
如果你让我摸你的小穴
I'd bet you'd feel really good
我相信你肯定会感觉很好
if you let me touch your VJ.
谁说的
Who says thats--
真恶心
It's so gross.
等等  阴道是这么拼的吗
Wait, is vagina spelled with a J?
难道我一辈子都拼错了
Have I been spelling it wrong my whole life?
-不是  -我觉得
- No. - I feel like...
等等  他后来摸你了吗
Wait, so--so, did he touch your VJ?
那晚没有
Um, not that night.
我觉得我来大姨妈了
I think I had my period.
然后还有个女孩
Also there was a girl
在地板上爬着
crawling around on the floor
想拔了开关
unplugging lights.
不客气
You're welcome,
我是在营造气氛
I was trying to set the mood.
-我那时很爱诺亚  -我的天
- I loved Noah. - Oh, my God,
你简直是为他着迷
you were so obsessed with him.
他很可爱
He was very cute.
很可爱
He was cute.
好了  该谁了
Okay, whose turn is it?
等等  你呢  基拉
Wait, okay, what about you, Kaela?
我感觉自己完全不知道你的感情生活
I feel like I know nothing about your love life.
她正热恋着呢
Oh, she's hot and heavy with someone.
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
不是男人
Not a man.
其实是她
It's a woman, actually.
她叫弗兰基
Her name's Frankie.
我的天  太棒了
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
我都不知道你喜欢女孩
I didn't know you were into girls.
是啊  我喜欢姑娘
Yeah, yeah, I am.
我是说
Um...I mean,
高中时候我就喜欢姑娘
I--I was in high school too,
但太害怕不敢出柜
I was just too scared to come out.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你们怎么认识的
How'd you guys meet?
工作
At work.
她在儿科工作
She works in the pediatric department,
所以
so, yeah,
我们已经在一起一年了
it's been almost a year now.
其实我还没告诉你们
Oh, actually, I didn't even tell you guys this.
等她租期到了我们打算同居
We are gonna move in together when her lease is up.
-天哪  太好了  -恭喜啊
- Oh, shit, that's awesome. - Congratulations.
天哪  太棒了
Oh my God, that's amazing!
我们之前在讨论新年
We were just talking about like the new year
新计划什么的
and like goals and stuff,
然后就觉得应该
and it makes sense.
等等  先别说
Wait, save it.
我有个好主意
I have a really good idea.
大家好  我是丹妮尔
Hey, guys, it's Danielle.
我正和我高中最好的朋友在一起
I'm here with my high school besties
我们在分享各自的新年计划
and we were just talking about New Year's resolutions.
这是基拉
This is Kaela.
你的新年计划是什么
Okay, what are your resolutions?
好的  你知道吗
Okay, you know what,
我想多去户外走走
I would like to spend more time outside,
少盯着手机
less time on my phone.
我感觉自己一辈子都盯着屏幕
I feel like I spend like my entire life staring at a screen.
而且你知道吗  我真的很想
And you know what, I really want to be better
更好地帮助别人
about helping people, you know,
现在世界上
with all the stuff that's going on
发生了这么多事  我就感觉
in the world right now, I just feel like...
等等  妈蛋
Wait, shit.
我们得重新录
We need to start over.
我不想搞得有政治倾向
We try not to get like too political,
这样会让人们觉得无聊
'cause it tends to bum people out
或疏远那些与我政治倾向不同的人
or can alienate anyone that doesn't have my same politics.
你就说说感情生活吧
Um, maybe just like stick to your love life.
-好的  -嗯
- Okay. - Yeah,
我们从头录
we're just gonna start over.
大家好  我是丹妮尔
Hey, guys, it's Danielle.
我正和我高中最好的朋友在一起
I'm here with my high school besties
我们在分享各自的
and we were just talking
新年计划
about New Year's resolutions.
你的新年计划是什么
Okay, what's your resolution?
能够
Um, to--
能够和我女友保持良好的沟通
to maintain healthy lines of communication with my girlfriend
然后
and
每天都说我爱她
to tell her that I love her every day.
真甜蜜
Oh, so sweet.
我说了她是个小可爱
I told you guys she was a sweetheart.
好了  克洛伊
Okay, Chloe.
-大家好  -你的新年计划是什么
- Hi. - What are your resolutions?
减重十磅  找个男友
Okay, lose 10 pounds, get a boyfriend,
从我妈家搬出去
and to move out of my mom's house.
你可以的  克洛
Ugh, you can do it, Chlo.
最后一位
Okay, last but not least,
我穿一条裤子的好姐妹
my bestie from the nestie,
阿莱克西斯
Alexis.
不要
No.
来嘛
Come on.
说点什么
Say something.
有一百万粉丝会看到呢
It'll go out to a million followers.
你能用你的话语激励他们
You'll inspire them with your words.
我真的不想录
I really don't want to.
好吧  她以前在镜头前不那么害羞
Well, she didn't used to be this camera shy.
来嘛  你想要什么
Come on, what do you want?
健康  感情
Uh, health, relationship,
职业
career?
你有什么目标吗
I mean, don't you have any goals?
说真的  别拍了
Seriously, stop.
来嘛  莱克斯
Come on, Lex,
让全世界都看看你漂亮的脸蛋
just let the world see your beautiful face.
告诉他们你对未来的希望和梦想
Tell them about your hopes and your dreams for the future.
他们都很渴望听到你说
They're dying to hear from you.
快点  什么
Come on, what?
什么
What?
快点  莱克西斯
Come on, Lexie.
快点
Come on.
快点  阿莱克西斯
Come on, Alexis.
快点
Come on.
快点快点快点
Come on, come on, come on.
快点  告诉他们
Come on, tell them.
快点  阿莱克西斯
Come on, Alexis.
给世界看看你漂亮的脸蛋
Show the world your beautiful face.
把这愚蠢的相机从我眼前拿开  丹妮尔
Get that fucking camera out of my face, Danielle.
什
Wha...
什么鬼  阿莱克西斯
What the hell, Alexis?
我只是
I was...
我只是不想让你落单
I was just trying to include you.
我去检查下保险丝
I'll go check the fuse box.
哎呀
Yikes.
我以为窗户会碎
I...thought the window was gonna shatter
手机也会坏
and my phone was gonna be totally screwed.
我还在颤抖
I'm still shaking.
是啊  自从那次事故后
Yeah, um, Alexis's parents
阿莱克西斯的父母把这里
had the whole place like hermetically sealed
封得严严实实的
after the accident and...or whatever.
操
Fuck...
抱歉  我不想吓你一跳
Sorry, I didn't mean to startle you.
我只想下来和你说
I just wanted to come down here and say I'm...
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry, I...
我都不知道事故后你是第一次回来
I had no idea you hadn't been back since the accident.
对你来说肯定很难
That must be really hard for you.
听着
And, look,
我知道咱俩很久没见了
I know I haven't seen you in a while,
我不知道
and, I don't know,
也许感觉有点怪
maybe things feel weird
因为你都是从我的视频上了解的我
because you only get this idea of me from my videos,
但我还是我
but it's just me.
说真的  莱克斯
Like, seriously, Lex,
是我啊
it's me.
跟你一起去美容院做除毛手术
The same girl who you went to electrolysis with
除去下巴毛的那个女孩
to get her chin hair zapped off.
每周五晚上都和你
Same girl who you'd go into food comas with
暴饮暴食的那个女孩  只因为没人愿意和我们玩
every Friday night because no one wanted to hang out with us.
天哪
Oh, my...
你还记得吗
Do you remember that?
-记得  -我们管那叫什么
- Yeah. - What did we call it?
我的天
Oh, my gosh, uh,
厨师快车
Chef's Express.
我一直都在想你
I think about you all the time.
你是我最好的朋友
And you're my best friend.
你认识我的时间比其他人都久
You've known me longer than anyone,
你看见过我身上其他人没见过的地方
you've seen parts of me no one else has,
真的
like, literally,
你检查过我有没有痔疮
you checked my butt for hemorrhoids.
而且我不想
And there's no one else
和其他人一起过新年
who I'd rather ring the new year in with.
我很感激你请我过来
I'm so grateful you invited me back here.
而且你是一个
And you're just
出色坚强的女人
such an amazing, strong woman,
我非常敬佩你
and I admire you so much.
我为你感到骄傲
I'm so proud of who you've become.
我们去派对吧
Let's just fucking party.
这才是我认识的姑娘
That's my girl!
快十二点了
It's almost 12
我们还都没怎么醉
and we are not nearly drunk enough.
来吧
Come on.
好了  姑娘们
Okay, ladies,
还有一小时2018年就结束了
there is only one more hour left in 2018,
-意味着不准玩手机  -别啊
- so that means no more phones. - No!
只有我们这几个姑娘
Just us gals.
我们要庆祝
We are going to celebrate.
因为今年是我们最好的一年
Because this year is going to be our best year yet.
我们值得拥有
We deserve it.
敬更多更好更辉煌的未来
To more, more, more, and more.
-我的天  -不会吧
- Oh, my God! - Oh God, no.
八年级的舞蹈会
Eighth grade recital!
你们还记得这支舞蹈吗
Do you guys remember this dance?
记得  你逼我们跳了无数遍
Yes, you made us do it so many times.
我们现在重温过去
We are doing it again,
再跳一次
we're doing it again.
就现在  现在
Right now, right now.
是的  必须跳
Yes, we are.
-我不跳  -起来
- I'm not. - Get up.
我们需要所有队员  所有队员
We need the whole gang, whole gang.
我们必须跳  你必须跳
We have to do it, you have to do it.
大家一起来
Everybody.
七  八
Seven, eight.
好好  你来  轮到你了
Okay, oh, okay. You go, your turn.
好吧  我从来没有
All right, never have I ever...
-快说  -我从来没有
- Come on. - Never have I ever...
我从来没有在棕榈泉进行过轮流性爱
Never have I ever taken turns in Palm Springs.
-怎么样  -去你妈的
- How 'bout that? - Oh, fuck you.
等等  什么是"轮流性爱"
Wait, what the hell is "Taking turns"?
就是三人行
It's a threesome where it's like
克洛伊称之为棕榈泉三人行
what Chloe calls her Palm Springs Threesome.
-什么  -没错
- What? - Yeah.
也不算是三人行
Yeah, no, it's not exactly a threesome,
更像是
it's more like, um,
轮流做爱
well, taking turns.
就好比睡了一个人
Like sleeping with one guy
之后再睡另一个
and then another?
没错  就是这样
Exactly, yeah.
不仅仅是啪啪啪
It's not just fucking,
他们还轮流给我下面口
like they take turns going down on me.
-天哪  -不  挺好的
- Oh, my God! - Yeah, no, it's fine,
如果你问我  我觉得很有礼貌
it's very polite, if you ask me.
好吧  你在轮流之前你认识这些人吗
Okay, did you know these guys before you took turns?
-差不多认识吧  -我的天哪
- Sort of. - Oh, come on!
克洛伊  你得说完整的故事
Chloe, you have to tell the full story.
好了好了  我们称这个家伙叫点头男
Okay, okay, so we call this guy The Nodder.
-点头男  -快说快说
- The Nodder? - Tell her, tell her.
好吧  我和一些朋友出去开生日派对
Okay, so I was on a birthday trip with some friends,
然后我们租了个房子
and we rented this house.
然后我和其中一个小伙子搞上了
And I had started hooking up with this one guy.
他是一个朋友的朋友
He was like a friend of a friend.
-没错  -然后有个男人进屋了
- Right. - But then this other guy came into the room,
我们一直在亲热
and we were like getting going,
他就站在门口看着
and he kind of just stood in the door.
你懂的  盯着看
You know, just watching.
然后他慢慢地靠近
And then he kind of came a little closer.
最后坐在了床边
And then he sat on the edge of the bed,
然后我看了他一眼
and then I kind of looked at him
之后他朝我点了点头
and he nodded at me.
我朝他点了点头
And I nodded back at him.
然后我又朝床上的男人点了点头
And then I nodded at the guy I was in bed with.
然后他朝我点了点头
And then he nodded back at me.
然后一切就顺其自然地发生了
And then it sort of just happened.
是不是很疯狂
Isn't that crazy?
我还是不知道
I still don't understand
大家怎么都知道点头意味着做爱
how everyone knew that a nod means sex.
那还能是什么意思
What the fuck else is it supposed to mean?
-打招呼吗  -谢谢
- Hello? - Thank you!
但当你裸着时  就很明显啊
But when you're naked, it's pretty obvious.
这就像是一个暗号表示
I mean, it's kind of like code for like...
-让我加入  -没错  让我加入
- Let me get in there. - Yeah, let me get in there.
-是不是很疯狂  -每次听都觉得精彩
- Isn't that wild? - Never gets old.
总之
Anyway, okay, um...
我从来没有
Never have I ever...
初中毕业舞会时尿裤子
Peed my pants at junior prom.
-都没有人注意到  -就是你
- No one even noticed that! - You!
所以不算
So it didn't count.
说真的  幸亏有你们
Actually, thanks to you guys.
-没错  不客气  -你们还记得雅奈尔老师吗
- Yeah, right, you're welcome. - No, Mr. Yarnelle, you remember?
我的天
Oh, my God.
水洒在地上了
There has been a spill.
各位我重复一遍
Everyone, I repeat,
潘趣酒碗旁水洒在地上了
there has been a spill by the punch bowl.
他真是太奇怪了
He was so fucking weird.
-我觉得他很可怜  -为什么
- I feel bad for him. - Why?
因为他看起来很孤独
Because he seemed like a lonely guy.
好吧  我从来没有
Okay, never have I ever
忘记刷牙
forgotten to brush my teeth.
什么
What?
真无聊
So boring.
随便了  好吧
Whatever, okay.
大家都该喝酒
Everyone should be drinking,
你们肯定都忘记刷牙过
you've all forgotten to brush your teeth.
-我知道  -我没有
- Yeah, I know. - I haven't.
但我知道如果不说些限制级话题
But I knew you wouldn't drink at all
你们都不会喝酒
if we didn't do some PG ones.
-没错  -我也做过坏事
- That's true. - I've done stuff.
-比如  -还没轮到我
- Like what? - Well, it's not my turn,
所以我没必要说
so I don't have to say,
但我能告诉你我做过坏事
but I'm just saying I've done stuff.
-读书和织毛衣  -随便吧
- Reading and knitting. - Whatever.
我有个好问题
I have a really good one.
我从来没有
Never have I ever
跟名人上过床
hooked up with a celebrity.
谁
Who?
谁谁谁谁
Who? Who? Who? Who?
谁
Who?
丹妮尔  快告诉我
Danielle, fucking tell us.
我签了保密协议
I signed an NDA.
我不能
I literally,
法律不允许我告诉你们
legally cannot tell you who.
开什么国际玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
是我们啊  我们还能告诉谁
It's us, who the fuck are we gonna tell?
我们只认识彼此
We only know each other.
快告诉我  求你了求你了
Fucking tell me, please, please.
给我个提示  小小的提示  拜托
Just a hint, a little one, please.
-拜托  -好好好
- Please. - Okay, okay, okay, okay.
-一个小小的提示  -好
- A tiny hint. - Okay.
电动
Electric...
汽汽车车
caaarrrss.
电动汽车
Electric cars.
我的天
Holy shit.
他差不多是全世界
He is like the richest man
最富裕的男人
in the entire world.
-真的吗  -是啊
- He is? - Yes!
你们怎么认识的
How did you meet him?
他给我打电话
He called me.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
我知道  很疯狂
I know, it was crazy.
我坐在马桶上
Um, I was sitting on the toilet
剪着脚趾甲
clipping my toenails,
然后接到一个电话
and I got this call.
他助手给你打的吗
Like from an assistant?
不  直接找我
No, directly.
什么  他直接打电话给你的吗
What, he just called you on the phone?
是的  我想
Yeah, I guess, um,
应该是我的经纪人给他我的号码
he got my number from my manager and...
等等  好吧
Okay, wait, okay,
他直接给你打了电话
so he just called you on the phone
问你要不要一起来一炮吗
and asked you if you wanted to hook up or?
不  他没有问我要不要来一炮
No, he didn't ask me if I wanted to hook up.
他45岁左右
He's like 45.
他约我出去
He asked me out.
上帝啊
Thank God.
他怎么知道你的
How did he even find out about you?
和大家一样
Same way everyone else does.
少来了
Get the fuck out of here.
他看你的视频吗
He watches your videos?
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
怎么
What?
他看上去那么...睿智
He just seems so...smart.
对啊
I know, right,
他不是第一个
I mean, he's not the first person
我没想到是我粉丝的人
who I would think is a fan,
但是他应该和一个我经常帮忙调配果汁的演员
but this actor who I, like, give juices to
是朋友
is a mutual friend,
我想应该是他给他看了我的视频
and I guess he showed him my videos.
等等  所以你的演员朋友
Wait, okay, so the actor friend,
是莱奥吗
is that Leo?
是莱昂纳多  对吗
It's Leonardo, isn't it?
是莱昂  你和莱昂睡了吗
It's Leo, did you sleep with Leo?
-你走火入魔了  -丹妮尔
- You're obsessed. - Danielle,
你和莱昂睡了吗  -没有  算了
- did you sleep with Leo? - No! Okay, you know what,
我们还是继续玩游戏吧
let's just get back to the game.
别跟我说你和他也签了什么该死的
Don't tell me you have some fucking bullshit NDA
-保密协议  -我没有和莱昂睡
- with him too. - I did not sleep with Leo.
但你的确是他的朋友  对吗
Okay, but you're friends with him, right?
-关系很铁  -是的  差不多吧
- Like you're tight? - Yeah, I mean kind of.
他很喜欢我的果汁
He likes my juices.
我想也是
I bet he does.
你好恶心
Ew, that is so gross.
太疯狂了
This is insane!
那他带你去了哪里
Okay, so where did he take you?
我刚告诉你们我从来没有和他一起出去约会
I just told you I never went out with him.
不  她说的是电动汽车先生
No, she's talking about Mr. Electric Car.
其实不算是真正的约会
Well, it wasn't exactly like a date.
这简直跟拔牙一样痛苦  丹妮尔
Okay, this is like pulling teeth, Danielle.
上帝啊  你最好赶紧说
Jesus Christ, you better dish.
我要杀了你
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
没什么好说的
There's not much to tell.
很短  而且
It was brief and...
我不知道
I don't--I don't know,
有点奇怪
kinda weird.
怎么奇怪
How was it weird?
伙计们  我真的
Okay, you guys, I'm like really
不应该说这些事
not supposed to talk about this.
拜托  伙计们
Yeah, come on, guys,
如果她不想说
if she doesn't want to talk about it,
她就不用说
she doesn't have to talk about it.
拜托
Oh, come on.
如果她说她不能说  那她就是不能说
If she says she can't talk about it, she can't talk about it.
基拉  拜托
Kaela, give me a break.
她都不肯老实说她
She can't just like drop that she's fucking
上了硅谷的王
the king of Silicon Valley,
还想让我们就这么
and expect us to be like,
"好吧  那我们就不提了"
"Oh, okay, we'll just drop it."
她可以  伙计们  因为
She can because, guys, we're playing a game.
我们继续回到游戏上
Let's just get back to the game.
-我继续来  -好吧
- I'll take my turn again. - All right.
好吧  我从来没有...
Okay, so, never have I ever...
不  这游戏就是这样  基拉
No, this is the game, Kaela.
我们得谈谈
We're supposed to talk about
我们的经历
the experiences that come up.
这才是重点
It's the whole fucking point.
是丹妮尔不遵守规则
Danielle's the one who's not playing it.
你不理解保密协议的概念吗
Do you not understand the concept of an NDA?
看来我们档次太低
I guess we're just too provincial
理解不了这么高端的概念
to understand such sophisticated concepts.
好吧  我们休息一下
Okay, let's take a break.
我们就
Let's all just--
不  这真是胡扯
No, it's fucking bullshit.
我以为我们都是你最好的朋友
I thought we were your best friends.
你以为我们会告诉谁
I mean, who do you think we're gonna tell?
反正没人会在乎你和
Nobody gives a shit what you did
电子汽车先生干了什么
with Mr. Electric Car anyway.
差点就信了
Well, you could have fooled me.
好好玩这个游戏
Just play the fucking game.
我们度过了一个漫长的周末
We spent a long weekend together.
是吗
Yeah?
然后呢
And what?
他开加长汽车来接你
He picked you up in a limo?
他的确派车来接我
He sent a car for me, yeah.
然后呢
And?
Then what?
然后他带我上了他的私人飞机
Then he took me on his private plane.
然后我们飞到了他在希腊的小岛
And then we flew to his island in Greece
在那里共度了一个周末
and spent the weekend.
就是这样
That's it.
那我来理一理
So, let me get this straight,
一辆加长汽车开来接你
a limo picked you up
送你上了飞机
and took you to a plane.
飞机里是一个你完全不认识的人
Inside that plane was a perfect stranger
带你去了他的私人岛屿  上了你
who took you to his private island, fucked you,
然后你就再也没有他的消息
and then you never heard from him again.
莱克斯  够了
Lex, I think that's enough.
是这样吗  丹妮尔
Does that sound about right, Danielle?
我们继续吧
Let's move on.
那你基本上就是一个妓女
So you're a whore, basically.
轮到我了
My turn.
我从来没有
Never have I ever
欺负过一个温柔无辜的小女孩
bullied a perfectly sweet and innocent girl
导致她自杀
until she committed suicide.
喝吧  丹妮尔
Drink, Danielle.
给我喝
Fucking drink.
承认你自己做的事  丹妮尔
Admit what you did, Danielle.
承认你折磨凯尔西
Admit you tortured Kelsey
导致她从窗户跳了出去
until she jumped out of a window.
那并不是什么该死的意外
It wasn't a fucking accident.
承认吧  你这个该死的贱人
Admit it, you fucking bitch.
十  九  八  七
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
六  五  四  三
six, five, four, three,
二  一
two, one.
新年他妈的快乐
Happy fucking New Year.
住手
Stop!
快点  把她绑起来
Now, quick, tie her up!
去拿气球  把她绑起来
Get the balloons, tie her up!
基拉  你在干什么
Kaela, what are you doing?
你同意这么做的
You agreed to do this.
救命
Help!
去拿椅子
Get the chair.
-喝  -给我喝
- Drink! - Fucking drink.
-天啊  -该死的凯尔西
- Oh my God, - Fucking Kelsey.
你们干什么
What the fuck are you guys doing?
好了  我开始拍了
Okay, I'm rolling.
不  还不行
No! Not yet.
怎么回事
What is going on, you guys,
你们在干什么
what are you doing?
时钟过了12点
Clock struck 12.
我要采纳《健康起来  丹妮尔》的建议
I'm taking Get Well Danielle's advice.
新的一年  新的我
It's a new year and this is the new me.
该把真相公之于众了
It's time to tell everybody the truth.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
当我们发现
When we found out
你要上电视了
that you were gonna be on TV,
我们就知道我们要阻止你
we knew we had to stop you.
我们不会让你站在
We're not gonna let you stand
几百万人面前
in front of millions of people
假装自己是完美的小公主
and pretend to be this perfect little princess
健康骗子女王
Queen of Wellness psychotic phony.
全世界都应该知道真相
The whole world deserves to know the truth.
我会告诉他们
And I'm gonna tell them.
我会告诉全世界
I'm gonna tell the whole fucking world.
我要毁掉你的人生
I'm gonna ruin your life.
你那完美的小人生都是基于谎言的
Your whole perfect little life is based on a lie.
你是个骗子  你是个烂人
You're a fraud, you're a terrible person.
你很邪恶  你霸凌所有人
You're evil, you bullied everyone.
你一直说克洛伊胖
You called Chloe fat all the time.
她患了两年的暴食症
She was bulimic for two years.
你说基拉
You called Kaela...
是个丑陋的女同性恋
an ugly lesbian.
她受到深深的伤害  到了二十多岁
She was so traumatized she didn't come out
才敢出柜
till her mid-fucking-20s.
-基拉  -闭嘴
- Kaela-- - Shut up!
凯尔西只是想要成为我们的朋友
All Kelsey wanted was to be our friend,
而你折磨她
but instead you tortured her.
你杀了她
You killed her.
然后你继续你的生活
And then you just moved on.
我知道那晚很痛苦
I know that night was traumatic.
我们俩都在场
We were both there.
我们俩都想成为她的朋友
We were both trying to be her friend.
不  我们没打算成为凯尔西的朋友
No, we weren't trying to be Kelsey's friend!
我们折磨她
We tortured her!
你告诉我们那样对她
You told me that fucking with her
是为了她好
was for her own good,
她是个又胖又丑的废物
that she was a fat, ugly loser
需要我们帮助她变好
who needed our help to become cool.
我从来没有这么说
Guys, I never said that.
我听了你的话
And I fucking listened to you.
我相信你
I believed you
因为你的权力凌驾于我
because you had power over me.
就像你统领着这一大群
Just like you've got power over this army
自恋的混蛋
of narcissistic little fucking brats
占领全世界
who are taking over the world,
传播并迷恋你的一派胡言
spreading and liking your bullshit
跟传染病似的
like it's a fuckin' disease.
你不配告诉人们要自爱
You do not deserve to tell people to love themselves
你这一辈子明明
when you've spent your entire life
都在让别人受尽折磨
making people feel like shit!
但以后再也不会了
But not anymore.
该告诉全世界
It's time to tell the world
你是一个多么恶劣的人
what a terrible person you are.
我觉得那...
I think that's, um...
我觉得那是个好主意
I think that's a good idea.
大家好
Hey guys.
我是丹妮尔
It's Danielle.
我在和我的朋友们一起
I'm just here with my friends
我们在聊一些非常深层次的事
and we were talking about some pretty deep stuff.
这个话题我在工作上
Stuff that actually speaks to an issue
也遇到过好多次
I keep coming back to in a lot of my work
我觉得我们都有这种困扰
that, um, I think all of us struggle with.
过去的罪孽
The sins of the past.
当我们执迷于
When we hold onto bad things
我们过去所做的坏事  那能...
we've done in the past, it can--
能对我们的身体
it can have all sorts of...
产生各种有害的影响
deleterious effects on our body.
痤疮
Acne,
肥胖
weight gain,
失眠
insomnia.
为了避免这些
So in order to avoid
可怕的生理反应
these terrible physical ailments,
我们需要放下我们的罪孽
we need to move through our sins.
我们需要忏悔
We need to confess.
我16岁时  我的一个朋友死了
When I was 16 a friend of mine died.
她叫凯尔西  她...
Her name is Kelsey, and she was...
是一名优秀的女孩儿
an amazing young person
拥有着光明的前景
with so much life ahead of her.
但是她的同学们却对她进行无情的嘲笑
But her classmates teased her mercilessly.
他们会叫她丑女
They would call her an ugly bitch,
废物
a loser.
她每天都会哭着从学校回家
She would come home from school every day crying.
当我想到
When I think about a...
一个可怜有无辜的女孩
poor innocent girl
遭遇这种事
going through something like that,
我就...
it just...
天啊  我就觉得恶心
gosh, it just makes me sick.
但我也有参与
But I was complicit.
我的罪
My sin...
是我根本没有去阻止他们
Is that I didn't do anything to stop them.
天啊
God.
天啊  这样说出来的感觉真是太好了
God, that feels good to get that off my chest.
那根本不是忏悔
That wasn't a fucking confession.
谢谢你给我的机会
Thank you for that opportunity.
天啊
God.
你对着镜头有点紧张吗
You feeling a little camera shy?
得用镜头对你进行特写吗
Gotta get camera ready before your close-up?
你喜欢吗
You like that?
别担心  这是无动物产品
Don't worry, it's all cruelty free.
阿莱克西斯  冷静点
Alexis, honey, calm down.
愤怒是一种垃圾情绪
Anger is a junk emotion,
放下吧
okay, let it go.
轮不到你来告诉我冷静
Don't you tell me to calm down.
我受够了听你说要爱自己
I'm fucking tired of feeling like shit
听得我自己都恶心
because you tell me to love myself.
爱你自己是全世界
Loving yourself is the most natural thing
最自然不过的事  亲爱的
in the world, sweetie.
人们在童年就忘记了
People unlearn it in childhood.
你知道他们为什么会忘记吗
You know why they unlearn it?
因为是被像你这种人给摧毁的
Because people like you torment them.
不
No.
莱克斯
Lex.
阿莱克西斯
Alexis!
你到底怎么回事
What the fuck is wrong with you?
你要去哪里
Where the fuck are you going?
盯住她
Watch her.
克洛
Chlo.
我不知道
I have no idea
莱克斯说的关于凯尔西的事
what Lex is talking about with Kelsey.
但她的确说了一些
But she did say something...
我曾经忽视的事
I may have overlooked in the past.
很抱歉我以前在高中
I am so sorry about the way I treated you
那样对你
in high school.
如果我可以收回我所做的一切
If I could take it all back,
我肯定会的
I would.
我已经不是当初的那个我了
I'm not that person anymore,
虽然说再多遍也不够
and I can't say it enough,
但我还是要说对不起
but I'm sorry.
非常感谢你这么说
Well, I appreciate you saying that.
谢谢
Thank you.
宝贝
Lovebug.
新年快乐
Happy New Year.
-我想你  -我也很想你
- I miss you. - I miss you too.
你今晚怎么不回来
Why don't you come back tonight?
你要睡在那里吗
Do you have to sleep over?
嗯  我的车坏了  所以我得...
Yeah, my car broke down, so I have to--
我被困在这边了
I'm just kind of stuck here.
我得等阿莱克西斯
I gotta wait for Alexis
把我捎回去  所以
to give me a ride back down, so...
你要我来接你吗
Do you want me to come get you?
不用
No.
不用  我准备直接去休息了
No, I'll just go to sleep
我们明天见
and I will see you tomorrow.
基拉  开门
Kaela? Open the door.
我就是不知道为什么
I just don't know why
有人会做出这种事
someone would do something like this.
即使我根本没有那样做
Like, setting aside the fact
也要到处宣扬
that telling people
是我霸凌凯尔西
I bullied Kelsey to death
而导致她的死亡
could destroy my career,
根本不管这样会毁掉我的事业
even though it's something I didn't even do,
那样不仅仅会伤害到我  克洛
it wouldn't just hurt me, Chlo.
还会伤害到很多其他人
It would hurt a lot of other people too.
很多年轻的女性来找我求助
Young women rely on me for help.
寻求我的鼓励
For inspiration.
我真的很为她感到难过
I feel really bad for her.
她对未来抱有么多的
Like, she had all of these hopes and dreams
希望和梦想  但是
about the future, but...
她就是什么都做不成
she just has nothing going for her,
没有潜力
and no potential.
是吗
Yeah?
我也是
Well, neither do I.
所以去你妈的
So fuck you.
什么
What?
克洛伊  不是那样的
Chloe, that is not true.
-这只是你自己这么告诉自己而已  -随便吧
- That is a story you tell yourself. - Whatever.
你很风趣
You're funny,
真诚
honest,
性感
sexy.
你能成为你想成为的任何样子
I mean, you can be whatever you want.
你根本不知道你自己有多么优秀
You have no idea how good you are.
-你好  -怎么了
- Hey. - What's up?
没什么  我上个厕所
Nothing, I just had to pee.
莱克斯  我从来没同意过这么做
Look, Lex, I never agreed to this, okay?
你本来说只是想吓吓她
You said that the plan was just to spook her
让她承认自己对凯尔西做的事
into admitting what she did to Kelsey,
但她说自己没有做过
but she said she didn't do that stuff.
基拉  当然是她做的了
Kaela, of course she did that stuff.
怎么  你觉得是我编的吗
What, you think I'm making it up?
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
我们绝对会逼问出来
Look, we're gonna get it out of her,
只需要再给她一点压力
we just need to push her a little further.
我感觉不是很好
I'm not comfortable with that.
我不会折磨人的
I'm not gonna torture someone.
你说什么呢
What the fuck?
我们没有折磨她
We're not torturing her.
好吧  随便吧
Fine, whatever.
我只是
I just--
我没有同意事情进行到这种程度
I didn't agree for it to go this far.
这种程度  你本来指望怎么样
This far? Well, what did you expect?
那房间里的那个女人是个疯子
The woman in that room's a psychopath
她害死了一个无辜的人
responsible for the death of an innocent person,
我们需要保护其他女孩不遭她的毒手
and we need to protect other girls from her evil.
丹妮尔不邪恶
Danielle's not evil.
听着  我本来
Look, I wasn't gonna--
我本来不想
I wasn't gonna bring this up
在其他女孩面前提这件事  但是
in front of the other girls, obviously, but...
杰西在找人
Jesse is looking for someone
来接替我的频道空缺出的位置
to take over my segment on their channel,
我可以来选择我的接班人
and I get to be the one to pick my replacement.
老实说
And to be honest,
我今晚来这里的一大原因
the main reason I came here tonight
是因为我感觉
was because I had a feeling
你可能很合适
you might be a good fit.
真的吗
Really?
我是认真的  克洛
I'm serious, Chlo.
你最好别耍我
You better not be fucking with me right now.
我为什么要耍你
Why would I be fucking with you?
你不如来洛杉矶
Look, why don't you just come out to LA
和我住一段时间
and...stay with me for a little bit?
我们可以一起
We can come up with a pitch
给你想个适合你的环节
for your segment together.
我能带你转转
I can bring you around,
把你介绍给别人
introduce you to people.
男人们
To guys.
肯定会很有趣
I mean, it'll be really fun.
嗯
Yeah.
克洛伊
Chloe.
我知道你很受伤
I know that you're hurting.
我知道你用你的玩笑来掩盖你的痛苦
I know the pain you're covering up with your jokes.
我知道你很孤单
I know you're lonely.
我知道你很担心你的母亲
I know you're worried about your mother.
但我可以为你改变这一切
But I can change all of that for you.
我们可以改变那一切
We can change all of that.
一起
Together.
我们只需要先解决眼前
We just gotta deal with this situation first.
她专门挑
She's preying on people
跟凯尔西一样没安全感的人下手
who are as insecure as Kelsey was.
如果那还不算邪恶
If that's not evil,
我不知道什么还算
then I don't know what is.
也许她没有直接说他们是没用的废物
Maybe she doesn't call them vile losers,
但她绝对让他们将自己与她对比时
but she sure as hell makes them feel like that
有这种感觉
when they compare themselves to her.
而且她还会
And she's doing it all
披着帮助人的外衣
under the guise of helping people.
-也许她是在帮助人  -不要有这种想法  基拉
- Maybe she is. - Don't start, Kaela.
你之前同意这么做的
You agreed to do this.
不能中途放弃
You're not bailing.
阿莱克西斯  阿莱克西斯
Alexis--Alexis!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
绑得更紧点
Tightening the ties.
真相早晚会浮出水面  丹妮尔
The truth is gonna come out, Danielle.
不管用什么办法
One way or another.
我们不会放过你
We're not gonna leave you alone
除非你承认
until you admit
你对凯尔西做了什么
what you did to Kelsey.
莱克斯
Lex.
那道疤不是我给你留下的
I didn't give you that scar.
而是凯尔西
Kelsey did.
克洛伊  住手
Chloe, stop!
伙计们  你们要受到惩罚
Guys, you're being punished.
怎么回事
What's going on?
她们把我们锁在了这里
They locked us in here.
我们出不去
We can't get out.
伙计们  拜托
Guys, come on, please.
伙计们
Guys.
她不会让我们离开这儿的
Fuck, she's not gonna let us out of here.
她疯了
She's fucking insane.
她他妈的疯了
She's out of her fucking mind.
她们不会来的  基拉
They're not gonna come, Kaela.
好吧  但是克洛伊会来的  克洛伊
Fine! But Chloe will come. Chloe!
不  她们俩都不会来的
No, neither of them are gonna come.
我告诉你  她疯了
I'm telling you, she's fucking insane.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你才疯了  阿莱克西斯
You're insane, Alexis!
拜托  拜托
Come on, guys, please, please!
别浪费体力了
Stop wasting your energy.
那怎么办
So what?
就这么死在蒸汽房里吗
Just gonna die in a steam room?
我当初是想如果我同意这样做的话
I thought if I just went along with this,
你可以结束这一切
you could get some closure
开始新的生活
and move on with your life.
所以呢
So what?
她取笑我是同性恋
So she made fun of me for being gay.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我有一个很棒的女朋友
I have a great fucking girlfriend
我可能再也见不到她了
who I'm maybe never gonna see again
因为我要死在蒸汽房里了
because I'm gonna die in a steam room.
这太蠢了
This is so stupid.
你不想想起她吗
You don't want to think about her?
那就别上"照片墙"
Don't go on Instagram.
谁会在乎她是不是网红呢
Who cares if she's some dumb internet celebrity?
你不必看她的动态
You don't have to look at her stuff.
你为什么不走出去  或者找条狗
Why don't you go outside or get a fucking dog?
像你一直说的那样  完成你的学业
Finish your degree like you're always talking about.
你们这些人太愚蠢了
You guys suck so fucking much.
你们是全世界最蠢的人
You're the stupidest fucking people in the entire world.
操
Fuck.
操他妈的
Jesus fuck.
弗兰基来电
吸气
Inhale.
然后说一遍咒语
And now repeat the mantra.
没有什么能够阻挡我的向往
Nothing stands between me and all of my desires.
很好
Perfect.
当你感到思绪神游或是焦虑的时候
So any time you feel your mind wandering or you're getting anxious,
反复多念几遍这句咒语
just repeat that mantra as many times as you need
然后你会对接下来发生的事感到惊讶的
and you will be amazed at the things that start to happen for you.
没有什么能够阻挡我的向往
Nothing stands between me and all of my desires.
没错
Yes.
还要多久
How much longer?
我觉得几个小时就好
Um, I think a couple hours should be fine.
然后呢
What then?
然后我们报警
Then we'll call the cops,
告诉警察  在我们看电影的时候
tell them that they got stuck in the steam room
她们被困在了蒸汽房里
when we were watching a movie,
我们找到她们的时候  她们已经死了
and they were dead when we found them.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
怎么了
What?
我以为我们的计划只是
I--I just thought the plan was, like,
吓唬她们
to scare them, you know,
这样她们就不会散播谣言之类的了
so they wouldn't spread lies or whatever.
是的  是这样
Oh yeah, no, it was.
如果我相信她们不会散播那些
I mean, if I trusted that they wouldn't spread
足以毁掉我们的谣言的话
these terrible rumors that could ruin us,
我就会放她们走  但是...
I would let them go, but...
在这方面你比我更了解她们
I mean, you know them better than I do at this point.
记住  你有权掌控生活中的一切
And remember, you have utter power over everything in your life.
你可以完全放心地拒绝任何事情
You can say no to anything with complete ease and trust.
如果你觉得吓唬她们就能让她们闭嘴
If you think scaring them is enough to shut them up,
那我们就吓唬她们
then we'll just scare them.
我觉得可能可以
I mean, probably, yeah.
好  那我们就吓唬她们
Okay, then we'll just scare them.
好
Okay.
我只是...
I mean, I would just...
很担心如果我们放她们走了
be nervous that if we let them go
她们会继续传播那些可怕的谣言
and they spread these terrible rumors,
你知道网上的喷子都是什么心态吧
I mean, you know how it is with mob mentality on the internet, right?
在被证明有罪之前都不是无辜的
It's not innocent until proven guilty.
好吧
Right.
或许她们会告诉警察  我们想杀了她们
Or they would tell the cops we were trying to kill them
尽管我们只想吓唬吓唬她们
even though we were just trying to scare them.
但说实话  无论你怎么想
But honestly, whatever you think.
我不想做一些让你感觉不舒服的事
I don't want to do anything that makes you feel uncomfortable.
你相信她们会闭嘴吗
Do you trust them not to say a word?
没有什么能够阻挡我的向往
Nothing stands between me and all of my desires.
该死
Shit.
拜托  基拉  继续
Please. Kaela. Go on.
没有什么能阻挡你的欲望
Nothing stands between you and all of your desires.
好吧
Okay.
糟糕  门被锁上了
Shit, shit, it's locked.
坏了  坏了
Fuck! Fuck!
她们肯定拿走了钥匙
They must have taken the key.
糟糕
Shit.
在搞我吗
Fucking me?
糟糕  打不开
Shit, it won't open.
操
Fucking--
再试试
Try it!
我打不开
I can't get it!
I can't get it.
操
Fuck.
快点  克洛伊  你在搞什么
Come on, Chloe! What the fuck?
快走
Let's go!
等等
Wait.
克洛伊  快点
Chloe, come on!
去找到她们
Go find them.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
很抱歉我把你卷了进来
I'm so sorry I dragged you into this.
没事
All right.
我不知道这是怎么了
I don't know what's going on.
她真是疯了
She's totally crazy.
我要把我们弄出去
I'm gonna get us out of this.
-怎么弄  -我不知道
- How? - Fuck, I don't know.
我需要时间想一想
I just -- I need a second to think.
所有的窗户都被封死了
All the windows are sealed.
如果我能拿到我的手机
If I can just--if I can just get to my phone.
她们拿走了我们的手机
They took our phones.
我知道  但肯定就在楼下
I know, but they must be somewhere downstairs.
如果我能拿到手机  我就能报警
If I can just get to my phone then I can call the cops.
不  阿莱克西斯  听我说
No, Alexis, Alexis, listen,
听我说  别一个人出去
listen to me, do not go out there alone.
-我要去补救这一切  -别
- I'm gonna fix it. - No.
阿莱克西斯  别  阿莱克西斯
Alexis, no, no, Alexis.
没有什么能够阻挡我的向往
Nothing stands between me and all of my desires.
你们在里面吗
Are you in here?
基拉
Kaela?
阿莱克西斯
Alexis?
没事的  就我一个人
It's okay, it's just me.
-就我一个人  -阿莱克西斯呢
- Okay, it's just me. - Where's Alexis?
她不在这里
She's not here, okay?
我们都是孤身一人
We're all alone.
听我说  克洛
Listen, Chlo.
我不知道丹妮尔跟你说了什么
I don't know what Danielle said to you,
但我们可以从这一切中脱身
but we can still walk away from this.
好吗
Okay?
你和我
You and me,
我们可以离开这里
we can just walk away.
我们需要做的
All we need to do is just...
就是打电话报警  告诉警察她疯了
just call the cops and tell them that she went nuts.
我不可能打电话报警
There's no fucking way I'm calling the cops.
不可能
No fucking way.
克洛伊  我不会告诉警察你参与到其中
Chloe, I would never tell them that you were part of this.
我不会这么做的
I would never do that.
克洛伊  拜托
Chloe, come on.
你相信我  对吗
You trust me, right?
听我说  我们可以...
Look, we can just...
我们可以离开这里
We can just leave.
我们现在就得走了
We gotta go right now.
你现在就可以转身离开
We can just walk away right now.
好吗
Yeah?
拜托  克洛伊  就咱们两个
Come on, Chloe, you and me.
相信我
Trust me.
我们可以回家
We'll just go home
然后回到我们的正常生活
and we can go back to our normal lives, okay--
我不想回到正常生活
I don't want to go back to my normal life.
克洛伊  拜托  别这么想
Chloe, come on, stop it.
我的正常生活像屎一样
My normal life is shit.
放开我  你弄疼我了
Let go of me, you're hurting--
-你就想让我继续不起眼下去  -放开我
- You just want me to stay small. - Stop it!
你不想让我成功
You don't want me to succeed!
放开我
Let go of me!
操
Fuck!
出来吧  莱克斯
Come out, Lex!
我们不想伤害你
We weren't trying to hurt you.
我们只是想吓唬你
We were just trying to scare you.
如果你保证不再说凯尔西的那些事
And if you promise not to say anything about this Kelsey stuff,
我们可以当这一切没发生过
we can just let all of this go.
基拉
Kaela.
Kaela!
不
No.
糟糕
Ow, fuck!
操
Fuck!
怎么了  克洛
What's wrong, Chlo?
我...
I...
我杀了基拉
I killed Kaela.
天呐  克洛
Wow, Chlo.
那是意外
It was an accident.
我抓住了她
I--I went to grab her
然后她...我的老天
and she just--oh my God.
我真为你骄傲
I'm so proud of you.
你终于把你自己放在第一位了
You're finally putting yourself first.
这样才能实现你的梦想
That is how you achieve your dreams.
我感到很骄傲
I'm really impressed.
你在争取你一直想要的一切
You're really manifesting everything you've always wanted.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
是一场意外
It was an accident.
意外难免会发生
Accidents happen.
我们唯一能控制的
The only thing we can control
就是如何处理我们现有的情况
is how we handle our given circumstances.
而你处理得很好
And you handled it so beautifully.
没有什么能够阻挡我的向往
Nothing stands between me and all of my desires.
是谁在按门铃
Who the fuck is that?
糟糕  是弗兰基  基拉的女朋友
Shit, it's Frankie, Kaela's girlfriend.
她来干什么
What the fuck is she doing here?
我他妈怎么会知道
How the fuck should I know?
我们怎么办
What do we do?
好吧
Okay. Um...
有人吗
Hello?
我有办法了
Okay, I've got it.
我们放她进来
We let her in.
当她走神的时候
When she isn't looking, you get the knife
你拿把刀  把她处理了
and you take care of her, okay?
警察来了之后
Then when the cops come,
我们就说她来这儿是因为
we'll say that she showed up in a fit of jealousy
基拉和她分手了  她很嫉妒  想报仇
because Kaela broke up with her and she wanted revenge.
天呐  你真擅长撒谎
God, you're good at this.
这个故事编得很完美
And it's kind of an amazing story
因为我可以为自己辩称正当防卫
because then I can do a whole segment on, like, self defense.
你同意这么做吗
You okay to do this?
好吧
Mm-hm. Okay.
让她进来
Let her in.
好
Okay.
弗兰基  你好
Frankie, hey!
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
基拉之前打电话给我
Um, Kaela called earlier, so I...
天呐  你就是弗兰基
Oh my God, you're Frankie!
我的天
Oh my God.
见到你很高兴
It is so nice to meet you.
我久仰你的大名
I have heard so much about you.
基拉特别爱你
Kaela is absolutely in love with you.
我也特别爱她
Well, the feeling is mutual.
我是丹妮尔
I'm Danielle.
-很高兴见到你  -我也是
- Nice to meet you. - You too.
久仰大名
Heard a lot about you.
真好
That's sweet.
基拉还好吗
Is Kaela okay?
不然呢
Yeah, why wouldn't she be?
当然还好啦
Of course.
这话是什么意思
What do you mean?
她看起来很心烦
She just seemed upset and...
而且她不接电话
uh, she's not answering her phone.
她很想你啊
Oh, she just missed you.
她已经睡着了
She already fell asleep.
女生都会闹小脾气  对吧
I mean, classic K, right?
没错  她沾枕头就着
Yeah, she's pretty much head to pillow.
我忘了点事  失陪一下
Oh, shit, I forgot something. sorry.
她坚持到了12点吗
Did she make it to midnight?
是的
She did.
其实我们都坚持到了
Actually we were very proud.
我妹妹为你痴迷
My sister is obsessed with you.
她看你所有的视频  做锻炼
She watches all your videos, does all your workouts.
不吃奶制品  不吃麸质
Um, no dairy, no gluten,
她对你宣传的果汁很感兴趣
and she got really into the juices you advertise,
就是那个  有很多蔬菜的那个
the, uh... Very Very Vegetables.
-是的  -没错
- Yes. - Yeah!
没错  有很多蔬菜的那个
Yes, the Very Very Vegetables.
你需要我看一下保险丝盒之类的吗
Do you want me to take a look at the fuse box or anything?
你人真好
Oh, you're so sweet.
不用了  没事的
No, it's okay.
反正我们也要去睡觉了
Um, we're heading to bed soon anyway.
好吧
All right.
天啊
Holy shit.
干得漂亮  克洛
Good job, Chlo.
过来
Come here.
你还好吗
Okay?
你干得很漂亮
You did so good.
我们会把你送到洛杉矶
We're gonna get you to L.A., okay?
我们今晚就把你送走
We're gonna get you out of here tonight.
你会得到你想要的一切
You are gonna get everything you've always wanted.
没有什么能够阻挡我的向往
Nothing stands between me and all of my desires.
是时候向前看了  阿莱克西斯
It's time to move on, Alexis.
是时候治愈你自己了
It's time to say yes to healing.
是时候放下过去了
It's time to say yes to letting go.
你的生活不必太紧张
Your life doesn't need to be tight.
可以很轻松的
It can be messy.
-不要再克制和遵守规矩了  -没有什么能够
- Let go of control and order. - Nothing stands between me...
-你只是大海中的一根针  -阻挡我的向往
- You're just chum in the water. - ...and all of my desires.
放弃吧
Give up.
从容接受你的命运吧
Relax into your destiny.
克洛
Chlo!
我的天
Oh my God!
别再以自我为中心了
It's time to stop doing the ego dance.
别再向外界寻求认可了
Time to stop looking to the outside world for validation.
我感觉你内心充满了力量  阿莱克西斯
I see so much strength in you, Alexis.
你只是被误导了
You're so misguided.
让我来帮帮你吧
Let me help you.
我们不应该是敌人
We're not supposed to be enemies.
莱克斯  如果你真的以为
Lex, if you thought for one fucking second
我会承认凯尔西是因我而死
I was gonna admit Kelsey died 'cause of me,
那你真是比我想的更蠢
you were a bigger fucking idiot than I thought.
我是个富婆
I'm fucking rich.
你明白吗
Do you get that?
人们崇拜我
People worship me.
而这只是个开始
And this is just the beginning.
我会上杂志  上电视  演电影
I'm gonna have magazines, tV shows, movies.
我要去拍电影
I'm gonna be in movies
你觉得我会让这个机会溜走吗
and you think I'd throw that all away?
你毁了我的生活
You ruined my life!
你夺走了一切
You took everything!
我受够了
I got stuck with this.
本来是我
It should have been me.
应该是我的
It was supposed to be me.
我那么努力
I worked so hard!
你觉得应该是你
You think it was supposed to be you,
你这个可悲的傻蛋
you pathetic piece of shit?
你是个废物
You're a fucking loser!
你狗屁不是
You are nothing!
你这个透明人
You're invisible!
你这个可悲的傻蛋
You pathetic piece of shit!
你永远达不到我的高度
You could never achieve what I've achieved.
你永远得不到我所拥有的
You could never have what I have.
你狗屁不是
You are nothing!
我掌管我自己的命运
I control my destiny!
我掌管着我所拥有的
I control what I hold onto,
我掌管着我所放弃的
and I control what I let go!
各位好
Hey guys.
正如你们所得知的那样
As I'm sure many of you heard,
我们亲爱的朋友和播主
our dear friend and contributor
《健康起来  丹妮尔》在新年当天
Get Well Danielle passed away
去世了
on New Year's Day.
今天和我们一起纪念她的
And here with us today to help us remember her
是她最好的朋友  阿莱克西斯
is her best friend, Alexis.
感谢你今天前来  阿莱克西斯
Thank you for joining us, Alexis.
谢谢你们邀请我
Thank you for having me.
我看了新闻报道
So, I read on the news,
我不想讲得太可怕
and I don't want to get too gruesome here,
但是是你们一个朋友吃醋的恋人干的吗
but it was a jealous lover of one of your friends?
是的  丹妮尔鼓励我们的朋友基拉
Yes, Danielle had encouraged
她值得拥有更好的生活
our friend Kaela that she deserved better,
她应该开始全新的一年
that she should start the new year fresh
找一个真正爱她的人
and find someone who really loved her.
我猜基拉的爱人很伤心  失去了理智
And I guess Kaela's partner just took it really hard and lost it.
你最想让全世界记住丹妮尔的什么
What do you want the world to remember most about Danielle?
很难挑出一件事
It's hard to just pick one thing.
她是个完美的人
She was a wonderful person.
我知道她不想让我沉浸在悲痛之中
And I know she'd just want me to move through this
她想让我过充实的生活
and live my fullest life.
这段经历教会了我许多
This experience has taught me so much,
特别是正当防卫的重要性
especially the value of self defense.
没错  今天你要教我们
That's right, you're gonna teach us today
如何手工制作防狼喷雾
how to make your own DIY pepper spray.
没错
Yes, I am.
包中要常备一样东西
Now there's one thing that you always need in your bag,
那就是防狼喷雾
and that's pepper spray.
我将给大家演示如何用日常材料
I'm gonna show you how to make your own pepper spray
制作防狼喷雾
using household ingredients.
太好了
Wow!
在我们开始之前
Now before we get started,
请确认你戴上了护目镜
please make sure you're wearing your protective glasses
和橡胶手套
and your Latex gloves,
因为这东西很辣
because this stuff is spicy!
我的天
Oh my gosh.
好的  我们需要醋  辣椒面
Okay, so we're gonna need vinegar, chili flakes,
红辣椒粉  油  一个碗和喷雾瓶
red chili powder, oil, a bowl, and a spray bottle.
别惹我哦  杰西
So don't cross me, Jess.
天呐  别喷我哦
Oh my gosh, stop it!
你要小心啦
You watch out!